# Steven Mtunzi Mavuma

## **Fullstack Developer**

Johannesburg, Gauteng 2189 st.vuma@gmail.com +27 81 451 1932

National identity Number: 8910155851084

I am an efficient and professional fullstack developer with knowledge and experience in creating applications with the MEAN stack . I am also efficient in PHP and MySql. I enjoy solving problems and learning new skills. I'm an effective communicator and can easily work with diverse individuals from different a abckgrounds. I am a team player who enjoys adding value to everything he does.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

## Work Experience

#### **Digital Media Publisher**

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints - Johannesburg, Gauteng November 2021 to Present

I design and edit web pages. I also publish content on internal cms portals, internal sharepoint sites and social media channels.

#### Media Graphic Designer & Web Developer

Mediafrika - Pinetown, KwaZulu-Natal November 2018 to June 2021

I designed visual content for social media, advertisements, and branding. I developed websites using html5, CSS, SASS, javascript, MySql, and PHP or designed websites using WordPress. I helped manage some WordPress installations as well as assisted with error troubleshooting and site migrations. I assisted with domain registrations, transfers, and assignments. I assisted with the creation of new Cpanel webmail accounts, setting up Html email signatures, and setting up emails on different email clients.

#### **Web Designer**

The Resolve - Durban, KwaZulu-Natal July 2016 to October 2018

I developed websites and carried out all graphic design work. I managed email marketing efforts. I ran paid advertisements on Social media, search engines, and display networks. I monitored analytics reports and optimized marketing efforts.

#### Education

## Associate of Applied Science (AAS) in Applied Technology

Brigham Young University-Idaho - Rexburg, ID

April 2019 to April 2021

### **Bachelors in Science**

University of Cape Town - Cape Town, Western Cape January 2009 to December 2012

#### **Grade 12**

Zwelihle High School 2008

#### Skills

- Wordpress (6 years)
- Adobe Indesign (1 year)
- Adobe Photoshop (2 years)
- Adobe Illustrator (1 year)
- HTML5 (5 years)
- CSS (5 years)
- NodeJS (2 years)
- Angular (1 year)
- PHP (3 years)
- Javascript (3 years)
- SASS (2 years)
- Express.JS (2 years)
- MySQL (2 years)
- MongoDB (1 year)
- Mongoose (1 year)
- Rest API (2 years)
- Git (3 years)
- Bootstrap (2 years)

### Languages

- IsiZulu Fluent
- IsiXhosa Fluent
- English Fluent
- Sotho Beginner

### Certifications and Licenses

## **Code 10 Driver's License**

October 2013 to Present

#### Assessments

## Attention to detail — Highly Proficient

August 2022

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions and detecting details from among distracting information

Full results: Highly Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

## Additional Information

#### Leadership skills:

- Leadership responsibilities.
- Diversity management.
- Basic communication.
- Teamwork and Strategic planning.
- Project management.